hi spring band in this week's
嗨，本周的春季乐队
installment spring tips we're going to
我们将要介绍的春季分期提示
look at the we're going to continue our
看看我们将继续我们的
look at the nice features in spring five
看看春季五的漂亮功能
and particularly features around the new
特别是新功能
spring webflix module which is the
spring webflix模块是
reactive web tier that sits adjacent to
与之相邻的反应式Web层
Spring NBC but works on us and supports
春季NBC，但对我们有效并提供支持
a reactive runtime right it's based on
基于它的反应式运行时权限
project reactor and some surfaces that
项目反应堆和一些表面
it that API and then abstraction in that
API，然后在其中进行抽象
way of thinking about things
思考事物的方式
always to to the component model that
总是对组件模型
use now some of it is very similar to
现在使用其中一些与
what you may use in spring MVC and what
您可以在Spring MVC中使用什么以及
you might be associated or might be a
您可能已经关联或可能是
use to in spring MVC but something
习惯于春季MVC，但是
that's different because of course the
这是不同的，因为当然
nature of the paradigm is different so
范式的本质是不同的
one thing that is different and I think
一件事是不同的，我认为
for the better is is how we can consume
更好的是我们如何消费
services right what is what an analogue
正确的服务是什么
do we have for the rest template in
我们有剩下的模板吗
spring webflix and similarly how do we
春天的webflix，以及我们如何类似
test you know from the client side
从客户端测试您是否知道
perspective services so in order to
透视服务所以为了
demonstrate that we're going to build a
证明我们将要建立一个
a reactive application and the
反应性应用程序和
application will take advantage of the
应用程序将利用
spring web list module which of course
Spring Web List模块当然是哪个
is provided by spring 5 which is do as a
由Spring 5提供
G anything by the summer so for now
到夏天为止什么都可以
we'll suffice ourselves you know satisfy
我们会满足你自己，你知道满意
ourselves to use the spring WA flex
自己使用Spring WA flex
module as support and spring boot to
模块作为支撑和Spring 引导至
that of snapshot so I'll bring in the
快照的内容，所以我将
reactive web support and I'll hit
反应性的网络支持，我来打
generate and in our application we're
生成并在我们的应用程序中
going to build a simple domain and I'm
要建立一个简单的领域，我
very much Imperial domain I don't want
我不想的帝国域
to spend too long on the actual service
花太多时间在实际服务上
I just want asked something with which
我只想问一些关于
we can you know play and experiment
我们可以知道玩和实验吗
right so here's our new service and I
对，所以这是我们的新服务，我
always forgive this I'm going to bring
总是原谅我要带的
in Lombok because I do have a simple
在龙目岛，因为我确实有一个简单的
entity that I want to I want to create
我要创建的实体
that you know it's tedious or why I
你知道这很乏味，或者为什么我
write the code by hand so say Lombok
手动编写代码，所以说龙目岛
okay now Lombok is a compile time
好吧，现在龙目岛是一个编译时间
annotation processor it's going to make
注释处理器
it trivial for me to you know build an
对我来说，琐碎的事
entity that we can work with I don't
我们可以合作的实体
really need I'm going to just create the
真的需要我要创建
client and the service in the same
客户与服务在同一个
project
项目
naturally in most examples they would be
在大多数情况下，自然会
in separate projects but
在单独的项目中，但
what I want to demonstrate is the point
我想证明的是重点
and not particularly how to spin up a
而不是特别如何旋转
new project on the extraneous Lancer
无关的枪骑兵的新项目
here so I'm going to have a service well
在这里，我要好好服务
let's go to base project called reactive
我们去叫反应性的基础项目
alright we'll have a new service here
好吧，我们将在这里提供新服务
and a new client okay and in the service
和新客户都可以，并且在服务中
we want to create a reactive service
我们想创建一个响应式服务
application so just a typical spring
应用，因此只是典型的Spring
good application spring complete
良好的应用Spring 完成
application and we're going to make this
应用程序，我们将做这个
a rest controller and we'll provide a
rest controller ，我们将提供
public static void main string arguments
公共静态void主字符串参数
a callback array I method I'm going to
我将要使用的回调数组
say spring application run reactive
说春季应用程序运行反应
service application back class args good
服务应用程序返回类args好
now there's our there's our end point
现在有我们的终点
there's our best physical rest
有我们最好的身体休息
controller so far so good when you swing
挥杆动作到目前为止效果很好
to you know to move around to talk about
你知道四处走动谈论
so let's build an event what is the
所以让我们建立一个事件是什么
event all just any kind of DTO right we
事件所有任何类型的DTO对吧
don't care too much about the domain so
不太在乎域名，所以
shut the data you can have a field
关闭您可以拥有一个字段的数据
private long ID and it'll have a date
私人长ID，并且有日期
because why not
因为为什么不
alright so there we go there's our three
好了，所以我们走了，那里是我们的三个
fields and we should probably build an
领域，我们可能应该建立一个
all argument constructor very good now
现在所有参数的构造函数都很好
the first end point will just return a
第一个端点只会传回
single event by its ID right so it'll be
单个事件，其ID正确，因此它将
a mano that is to say a potentially
一个可以说是潜在的马诺
infinite infinitely stream or infinitely
无限无限流或无限
valued container object that in this
在此有价值的容器对象
case only has one right so it's going to
案子只有一项权利，所以它将
contain a simulant event by ID and the
通过ID包含模拟事件，并且
path variable will encode the ID and
路径变量将对ID进行编码，
we're not going to spend too much time
我们不会花太多时间
on this I would say minded that just
关于这一点，我想说的只是
we're just going to hard code it a new
我们只是要硬编码一个新的
bit right so I don't even have an I
有点正确，所以我什至没有
don't even have a database connected to
甚至没有连接数据库
the classification because it's really
分类，因为它真的
not what we care about this time right
这次我们不在乎
which wants something to work with
想要与之合作的东西
so that's what
那就是
these cases how to get one particular ID
这些情况下如何获得一个特定的ID
that's called a mano it's got a zero or
这被称为mano它的值为零或
one value and then the next case is
一个值，然后另一种情况是
we're going to revisit our service and
我们将重新考虑我们的服务，
event discussion from a previous video
上一部影片中的活动讨论
and we'll create an in point that just
我们将创建一个
returns records every second right so
每秒都会返回记录，因此
events and it's going to be a flux it's
事件，这将是一个变化
going to be a container that returns a
将是一个返回一个
potentially infinite number of values
潜在的无限数量的值
right so a flux of events and we don't
是的，所以一连串的事件，我们不会
want to generate actual events that are
想要生成实际事件
infinite right I don't want to call a
无限权利，我不想称呼
database that I want to line entropy so
我想对熵进行排序的数据库
I'll just create a continuous steady
我将创建一个连续的稳定
stream sort of based on the scheduler
流类型基于调度程序
right every second I want have a new
我想要的每一秒钟都有一个新
flux I wanna have a new event rather so
我想要一个新事件，所以
to do that I need to build a couple of
为此，我需要建立几个
events so build a couple of fluxes one
事件，因此产生了一些变化
for the events themselves right and this
对于事件本身是正确的，这
will just be easy because I'll build a
会很容易，因为我会建立一个
scheme I react a Java 8 stream and in
方案我反应一个Java 8流，并在
order to do that I can use a stream back
为了做到这一点，我可以使用流回
create method here generate rather and
创建方法在这里生成相当和
the generate method takes a supplier and
生成方法需要一个供应商，
the supplier just expects me to return
供应商只是希望我退货
the value so I can just hard code the
的价值，所以我可以硬编码
current time and the date and there we
当前时间和日期，然后我们
go that's my first one and then the next
那是我的第一个，然后下一个
one we want is a duration flux right so
我们想要的是持续时间通量，所以
I'm going to say give us write flex but
我要说给我们写弹性但
interval duration dot of seconds and
间隔持续时间（秒）和
there we go that's our flux that will
我们去那就是我们的通量
emit a new value whenever they you know
只要您知道，就发出新值
and the second is path and we're going
第二个是道路，我们要走
to merge these together so I'm going to
将它们合并在一起，所以我要
say it zip them together event flux and
说它把它们拉在一起事件流和
the duration flux and what we want to do
持续时间变化和我们想做什么
is to map each one map you know map the
就是将您知道的每个地图都映射到
resulting flux which we can have it's
我们可以得到的通量是
gonna be a two bolt and have a two
会是两个螺栓，并有两个
parameters so it's a tuple of two
参数，所以它是两个的元组
basically we're going to map the tuple T
基本上我们要映射元组T
git T to no sorry T one
git T到不后悔T一
and that we return it fine so that's our
而且我们还可以，所以这就是我们的
value there now this could be a method
值，现在这可能是一种方法
reference a little cleaner I think right
参考一点清洁工，我认为是对的
there we go
我们去
very good so those are our two
很好，那是我们两个
server-side events or two server-side
服务器端事件或两个服务器端事件
endpoints rather if we run this we cook
端点，如果我们运行它，我们会做饭
we can confirm that everything's working
我们可以确认一切正常
by using the command line here so let's
通过在这里使用命令行，让我们
see curl HTTP localhost 8080 full slash
请参见curl HTTP localhost 8080全斜杠
event four slash let's just say one okay
事件四斜线让我们说一个好吧
and now let's just try all of them there
现在让我们在那里尝试所有这些
we go so I like as I make requests I get
我们去，所以我喜欢我提出要求时
a new value every second sort of like a
每隔一秒就会产生一个新值
heartbeat or something like that right
心跳或类似的东西
so now I want to build a client okay
所以现在我想建立一个客户好
plus not sound reactive client
再加上没有声音反应的客户端
application what was that is something
应用那是什么
already run let's kill that and run this
已经运行了，让我们杀死它并运行它
Oh because intelligence confused because
哦，因为智力困惑，因为
I obliterate the first client in here so
我ob灭了这里的第一个客户
we'll just create it again run this one
我们将再次创建它，运行这个
alright let's try it again okay so that
好吧，让我们再试一次，这样
is working right heartbeat every second
每秒都在工作正确的心跳
and event 4/22 right so that's working
和事件4/22对，这样就可以了
right now
马上
in this case we have two different two
在这种情况下，我们有两个不同的两个
endpoints those are up and running let's
那些已经启动并正在运行的端点
build a client let's build a client to
建立客户让我们建立客户
actually talk to our service at the
实际上是在
exercise for example this service and
例如行使这项服务
event extreme so this is actually
事件极端，所以这实际上是
something that you couldn't really
你无法真正做到的
easily do with the rest template before
轻松处理其余模板
right so it's nice that we can do this
对，所以很高兴我们可以做到这一点
because we have a client that is able to
因为我们有一个能够
deal with reactive sort of payloads in
处理反应性的有效载荷
this case a particularly long or for
这种情况下特别长或
that perhaps never-ending payloads so
也许永无止境的有效载荷
we'll say reactive client application
我们会说反应式客户端应用程序
and because I've taken the lazy path
而且因为我走了懒惰的道路
here to keep it simple I've got to
为了简单起见，我必须
remember to change the port on which we
记住要更改我们所使用的端口
start this application otherwise it's
启动此应用程序，否则
going to start on the same port as the
将与
service since they're on the same node
服务，因为它们在同一节点上
and they're saving they're sharing the
他们正在保存，他们正在分享
same auto configuration so we'll create
相同的自动配置，因此我们将创建
a new spring boot application okay
一个新的Spring Boot应用程序好
reactive client application by class
响应式客户端应用程序按类
args and we say that's the Builder
args，我们说那是建造者
spring application builder
春季应用程序构建器
okay property is the most pass in a
好的属性是
single property here server dot port
单个属性在这里服务器点端口
equals 80 81 okay at the post or the
等于80 81，还可以
default which is a you know 80 which is
默认值是80
what these service itself is running on
这些服务本身正在运行什么
now let this we have a ample room to
现在让我们有足够的空间来
build a client so we need the spring one
建立一个客户，所以我们需要春天
flex client type it's called the web
弹性客户端类型，称为网络
client and you can initialize one rather
客户，你可以初始化一个
an empty one like this or one that's pre
一个空的像这样的
you know primed and pointing to a
你知道准备和指向
particular service endpoint so that's
特定的服务端点，因此
what we'll do here and then we can use
我们将在这里做什么，然后我们可以使用
that in our command line runner so we
在我们的命令行运行器中
can say command line Runner Demerol look
可以说命令行Runner Demerol外观
at inject our client accordingly and
在相应地注入我们的客户
what I want to do is I want to call that
我想做的就是打电话给那个
endpoint at a service an event endpoint
服务终结点事件终结点
and see the results now again think
然后看到结果，现在再想一想
about what we had to do before with the
关于我们之前必须要做的
rest of it the rest of the rest template
其余的其余模板
would get the payload and then pass it
将获得有效载荷，然后将其传递
to a converter well in this case see the
在这种情况下很好地连接到转换器
pail is infinite so we need to be a
桶是无限的，所以我们需要成为
little a little bit more intelligent
一点点更聪明
about how we handle the client how we
关于我们如何处理客户的方式
handle the results and thankfully that's
处理结果，幸运的是
mostly taken care of for us right if we
如果我们
call an endpoint that returns a million
调用返回一百万的端点
records bring the web put the web client
记录将网络带入网络客户端
won't want flinch right so we can say
不想退缩，所以我们可以说
client dot get dot URI I'm going to say
客户点获取点URI我要说的是
then we want to get the event in point
那么我们想把事件弄清楚
we can say that the that we're accepting
我们可以说，我们正在接受
a particular type of data right so media
一种特定类型的数据权利，因此媒体
type pick stream media type text event
类型选择流媒体类型文本事件
stream okay and then we'll say that when
流好，然后我们说
I make the actual quest so go ahead and
我进行实际的任务，所以继续
issue the request and then from there we
发出请求，然后从那里开始
have to take the response they CR the
必须接受他们的回应
client response and tell the work client
客户回应并告诉工作客户
how we want to convert it you know how
我们要如何转换它，您知道如何
which what kind of a body we expect to
我们期望什么样的身体
come back so what we want is a flux of
回来，所以我们想要的是
event client our class and again I'm
事件客户我们班，我再次
sharing the same event from the service
通过服务共享同一事件
implementation here but a
在这里实施，但
you know in a proper system you'd have
你知道在一个适当的系统中
two different types you might even have
您甚至可能拥有两种不同的类型
a client-side representation add EPO or
客户端表示形式添加EPO或
whatever and you'd use that accordingly
随便你怎么用
so now I'm going to take the results I'm
所以现在我要取得结果
going to consumables the results I've
要消耗掉我得到的结果
got now events coming in and all I'm
现在有活动来了，我就是
going to do is I'm going to write out
我要做的就是写出来
I'm going to acknowledge the fact that
我要承认一个事实
I've received an event science on easy B
我已收到有关Easy B的事件科学
T and this naturally lends itself to a
T，这自然很适合
to a mess Griffin okay now of course
乱成一团的格里芬现在可以了
it's worth noting that we could have
值得注意的是，我们可以拥有
done a lot of other things here you know
在这里做了很多其他事情
we could have applied any of the
我们可以应用任何
operators that you expect from flex and
您期望从flex和
so on we could have specified a lot of
所以我们可以指定很多
the convenience headers and cookies and
便利标题和cookie以及
things like that that we want in the
我们想要的东西
request so we have the ability to really
要求，所以我们有能力真正
change you know do interesting things
改变你知道做有趣的事情
with the request itself and the client
与请求本身和客户端
itself is not just limited to get you
本身不只是为了让你
know the lead in the head and all that
知道头上的铅等
stuff you can also contribute to a
您也可以为
filter right if you want and that
如果需要，可以正确过滤
returns that returns a web client so you
return返回一个Web客户端，所以您
can contribute a filter that gets then
可以贡献一个过滤器，然后
gets applied to also some it calls
也适用于它所调用的一些
that's an ideal place for example to
那是一个理想的地方，例如
insert things like authentication and
插入验证和
you know Jesus encoding or whatever you
你知道耶稣编码或任何你
need to let you can do that there so
需要让你在那里做
let's go ahead and run this web client
让我们继续运行此Web客户端
example now this is now going to run a
现在的例子现在要运行一个
port 8081
端口8081
and if everything goes right we should
如果一切顺利，我们应该
see on the console here the events being
在控制台上查看事件
delivered from the service invalid
从服务交付无效
source type did I go along so string
源类型是我沿着字符串走的吗
args all right now we're cooking so
args好吧，现在我们在做饭，所以
there's our heartbeat value you know
你知道我们的心跳价值
every second we see a new value so
每秒钟我们看到一个新值
that's working fine that's that
很好，就是这样
certainly it's working as we expected
当然，它按预期工作
and that would continue at infinitum it
而且会无限期地继续下去
would never run out of memory right it's
永远不会用完内存，这是
doing the right thing it's going to load
做正确的事情将要加载
a certain amount you know in a page it
您在页面中知道的一定数量
will render it and then preload and and
将呈现它，然后预加载和
so on but it doesn't load at all as I'm
等等，但是因为我
trying to - wait - the way in to try and
试图-等待-尝试的方式
convert it right okay so those are
正确地转换它，所以这些是
reactive client sometimes I don't want
反应性客户有时我不想要
actually use a client just a call to
实际上使用客户只是一个电话
another service center of this when I
当我另一个服务中心
test my service as though our client I
像我们的客户一样测试我的服务
want to confirm that
想确认一下
services working in terms of the way
服务工作方式
that client would deal with it right so
该客户会正确处理
this is a pseudo integration test and
这是一个伪集成测试，
this is one of the very loans features
这是非常贷款的功能之一
about Thea spring MVC modules that you
关于Thea spring MVC模块，您
have the ability to to sort of mock a
有能力模拟
client side perspective right as you
正确的客户端视角
call that service so I'm going to create
致电该服务，以便我创建
a test here and we'll demonstrate the
在这里进行测试，我们将演示
web test client that's new in the latest
最新的网络测试客户端
milestone of spring five okay
春天五的里程碑
so we'll use the usual spring runner-up
所以我们将使用通常的春季亚军
beretta
贝雷塔
so spring winter and we're going to
所以春天的冬天，我们要去
build ourselves a web test client okay
自己建立一个网络测试客户端
so private web test client this dot web
所以私人网站测试客户端这个点网
test client equals web test client stock
测试客户等于网络测试客户股票
and we have a couple of options here we
我们在这里有两个选择
can bind our web test client to actual
可以将我们的网络测试客户端绑定到实际
server this is different from the the
服务器这不同于
mock MVC thing before right before you
在您之前模拟MVC事情
were always talking to the application
一直在与应用程序对话
context itself you can do the same thing
上下文本身，您可以做同样的事情
here you can talk to the spring web flex
在这里您可以与spring web flex交谈
machinery in the same application
机械在同一应用中
context it'll you know in the process
您会在此过程中知道
and route everything through the same
并通过相同的路线
components but you're not actually
组件，但您实际上不是
connecting to a socket is sending a
连接到套接字正在发送
request in this case you can make your
在这种情况下，您可以要求
bind to a server and that might be you
绑定到服务器，那可能就是你
know maybe might be very useful they're
知道他们可能会非常有用
trying to do integration tests in
试图在进行集成测试
another project maybe we've got a sort
另一个项目也许我们有点
of a longer suite of tests that bloom
大量测试的结果
through actual endpoints right it can
通过实际的端点，它可以
bind to an application context bind to a
绑定到应用程序上下文绑定到
particular controller so you can
特定的控制器，因此您可以
actually instantiate the controller here
实际上在这里实例化控制器
the M the reactive service replication
M反应式服务复制
and pass that in there as well and then
并将其传递到那里，然后
of course if you know but if you've been
当然，如果您知道，但是如果您去过
following what we've been talking about
按照我们一直在谈论
in the spring and the spring v eccentric
在春季和春季v偏心
spring tips and you know that there are
春天的提示，你知道有
functional reactive endpoints and vente
功能性反应终点和排气
and the centerpiece of that API is a
该API的核心是
router function so you can pass that in
路由器功能，因此您可以通过
here and that actually has a you know
在这里，实际上有一个你知道的
that describes a a catalog of different
描述了一个不同的目录
endpoints and routing so let's see let's
端点和路由，让我们看看
try this one this is new so we'll do
试试这个，这是新的，所以我们会做
that well saying it that we want to use
好说的话，我们要用
a base URL or we can use a builder
基本网址，或者我们可以使用构建器
factory but we'll just use the base URL
工厂，但我们只会使用基本网址
of localhost 8080 okay we'll build that
8080的主机好，我们将构建
and with that it's not hard to call a
因此，不难称呼
particular endpoint so we can say this
特定的端点，所以我们可以这样说
but what test client touch get looking
但是测试客户的感受如何
very cylinder familiar here right this
这里非常熟悉的圆柱体
is very similar to what we did only use
与我们仅使用的内容非常相似
the web client itself and we want to
网络客户端本身，我们希望
call an endpoint by URL so here we can
通过URL调用端点，因此我们可以
just say events let's say 42 and then we
只是说事件，比如说42，然后我们
can say that we want to accept Jason all
可以说我们想全部接受杰森
right so we can say application JSON and
对，所以我们可以说应用程序JSON和
we can say that we want to actually then
我们可以说我们想要
issue the request and we can expect a
发出请求，我们可以期待
status to be you know is okay it'll be
您知道的状态还可以
at 200 in this case we expect and then
在这种情况下，我们期望在200
we can expect while we can assert all
我们可以期待，而我们可以断言所有
sorts of those things there as well like
那里的那些东西以及
the type of payload that we should get
我们应该得到的有效载荷的类型
back in the body of the response and the
回到响应的主体
presence or non presence of a particular
存在或不存在特定的
header etcetera but in this case I think
标头等，但在这种情况下，我认为
we have enough to go so let's go ahead
我们有足够的去做，所以让我们继续
and see what that looks like
看看看起来像什么
right so and this very good our test is
是的，这很好，我们的测试是
green
绿色
everything's happy of course we should
一切都快乐，我们当然应该
confirm the negative by you know seeing
确认否定即可
if we are if we try and confirm that
如果我们尝试并确认
it's a arrowing out by returning a 500
这是一个箭头，返回500
but it should fail right so let's go
但它应该会失败，所以让我们开始吧
ahead and start that up and there we go
向前并开始，然后我们去
so our tests are blazing fast we're not
所以我们的测试速度很快
waiting for a whole server to start up
等待整个服务器启动
or in this case we've already got it
或者在这种情况下，我们已经知道了
running but we wouldn't need to if we
运行，但如果我们不需要
use the application context for example
例如使用应用程序上下文
and we get the ability to do sudo
我们有能力做须藤
integration tests we can do a lot of
集成测试我们可以做很多事情
these very very quickly right now
这些现在非常非常快
Springwood flux itself of course is very
Springwood助焊剂本身当然非常
very fast so in this installment we've
非常快，因此在本期中，我们已经
looked at a how to consume services
看了如何消费服务
using the web client and the web test
使用网络客户端和网络测试
client we looked at how this is similar
客户我们看了这有什么相似之处
to the rest template into the mock MVC
其余模板放入模拟MVC中
sort of apparatus that you may be
您可能会使用的一种设备
familiar with and spring MVC proper and
熟悉并熟练掌握MVC
of course that those components are
当然那些组件是
still there right and it's also worth
仍然在那里，这也值得
noting that you
注意到你
use the web client with you know none
与您一起使用Web客户端一无所知
you can use it with traditional sort of
您可以将其与传统的
non reactive services there's no reason
非反应式服务没有理由
you couldn't just use the web client in
您不能只在
lieu of the rest template for example
例如，代替其余模板
right
对
either way you you have your choice so
无论哪种方式，您都可以选择
with that thanks very much for watching
非常感谢您的收看
the we'll see you next
我们下次见